hotstartsearch.com 2013-04-06

# Privacy Policy For Fast Free Search

Privacy Policy 

FastFreeSearch is fully committed and fully respects the protection For this reason, FastFreeSearch has adopted this privacy policy, which informs you of the various ways your personal information may be processed and used. FastFreeSearch promises to take the steps as documented within this privacy policy to process and use your information. This document is only in effect for services that are owned by FastFreeSearch. 

Sometimes, FastFreeSearch or any of its advertisers may send your computer something called a cookie. This is a small bit of data that stores information from the Web server onto your computer hard drive. Cookies are not capable of reading information that is stored onto your computer, nor is it capable of reading other cookies. Cookies are not capable of damaging your system, either. Cookies are used by FastFreeSearch in order to understand what parts of the FastFreeSearch website you visit or personalize so that future visits can retain the personalization from before. Some advertisers may also opt to use cookies in order to ascertain how frequently you have seen one of their advertisements. This information can be used to further enhance the promotions, content and banners that you will see when visiting the FastFreeSearch website. 

FastFreeSearch allows you to access some free features on the FastFreeSearch website. Your information may be used to submit notifications of services and products by FastFreeSearch through email or postal mail. This information may also be sent to some clients of FastFreeSearch so that the clients may submit to you promotional information in relation to the service for which you created your account, unless you have opted out of receiving such information. 

FastFreeSearch maintains a “no spam” policy regarding your information, which means it will never be rented, sold or otherwise provided to any third party without your express written consent. 

From time to time, FastFreeSearch may send emails with regard to new products and services by FastFreeSearch. Unless otherwise stated above, FastFreeSearch will not send the email to you if you have not yet agreed to receive it. Should you opt to input your postal address through any online form on the FastFreeSearch website, you agree that you may be subject to mailings from other companies. 

By using the FastFreeSearch website, you agree that this information may be collected and used as FastFreeSearch has specified in this privacy policy. In the event that FastFreeSearch wishes to change the policy, these policies will be posted to this page.
